[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What to you is the key revelation you would like to communicate to the outside world which defines this woman, Hillary Clinton?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, I think the key revelation, Piers, is that it's really sort of in total of the book this is a book about how she would govern.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Am I surprised that people like the late Senator Ted Kennedy or John Kerry or Claire McCaskill are on this hit-list given that they were effectively opposition to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Kennedy", "John Kerry", "Claire McCaskill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Isn't it Amie, there's no difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Exactly, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Are you sure of that -- or it's in the documents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "I mean, do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well educated ones, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Do the American people still care about Monica Lewinsky enough to punish Hillary at the ballot box because of something Bill did nearly two decades ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I don't think it matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Monica Lewinsky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "When you did this book and when you finished it, what do you think are the key negatives that you discovered against Hillary Clinton that people may think about and latch on to when they vote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, we tell the story.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Guilty or not guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Not guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "So how significant could that be when it comes to determining who actually gets the Democratic nomination?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBG", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I think pretty significant, you know, we point in the book that she doesn't really have many marquee achievement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "First of all, what happened in the bathroom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well I was taking a shower like a normal routine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick Cunningham"]}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", ",", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, we were going to dinner, we we're on the fifth floor going down to the first floor and I was my pilot Nick Cunningham and two of our mechanics that work on our sleds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Are you always this accident prone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "No, I, you know, I think it's just a misfortunate of situation in both scenarios.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "And how are you making sure you don't get trapped again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, our four-man had been in his one of the last events of the Olympic games and so our work started for that competition to get here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Holcomb"], "LOCATION": ["U.S.A.", "Vancouver", "Latvia", "Great Britain"]}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Are you worried about the Jamaicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "They're very talented group and it's excited to see how much coverage they are getting, and they're going to be one the tougher teams on the hill that, you know, looking at the field of competition, U.S.A. won piloted by Steve Holcomb they're the defending Olympic champions from Vancouver and they're going to be tough, the Russians are going to phenomenal, the Germans, the Canadians, Latvia, Great Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Does that strike you as weird after all this time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "What is the -- I mean, do you have to every single day of your life have people asking you if you're logical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Well, see other think -- what else do people say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ":", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "No, what they asked me for is to teach them to do the neck pinch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Is it only three seasons of it were ever made the TV show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["May"]}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "This May.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Yeah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I quite a long time ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What is this machine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "This is an oxygenator.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "And that's the breathing issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "IMOY: That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Catching oxygen, atmosphere, where's Scotty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "POS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Pump it up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "How many were you smoking at your peak?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "IMOY: I was smoking a couple of packs a day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Did you hang out together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "He is a lot older than I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "He is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Do you hang out with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I haven't seen him in a while now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What about the rest of the Enterprise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "You see them all occasionally at \"Star Trek\" gatherings once in a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "ORGAN: You're big on Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Do you like it as a social piece?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I'm on there because I have a granddaughter who runs a shop called Shop LLAP, live long and prosper, where she sells \"Star Trek\" related merchandise having to do with me and so forth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Is that a bit freaky, that moment when you see them all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "It's fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Ever scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "No, the favorite scene of any of the three seasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Well, what are you doing acting -- do you still act at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "No, no, I have wonderful life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "I mean, we all watch \"Star Trek\", didn't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Yeah, it was a great show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I'm very good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Life, where are you at now with yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Well, my sixth year is over.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Did you recognized in him a kind of parallel to what you've been through and how would you advice people to try and help them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "It's a difficult one, you know, because obviously, you know, when these things happen, you think about the families and the people they've left behind, you know, is that what I make it about me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Is it people that are just -- they have that stricken them about old manner of things not just drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I think in my case, I mean, I don't know if -- about anyone else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "What would you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "It's quite an honor to say that about yourself, but, I remember, instead of going to the studio, and you know, everybody was like sort of in recording mode.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "What advice would you give to people who are famous and have to come out because that brings with it a particular thing, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Well, one of the fine things about coming up publicly is that people always encourage you to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", ":"], "qSentId": 629, "question": "How many times in your life Boy George have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I would say at this point, I don't think I've ever really truly been in love which...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "... is quite of shocking thing to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Do you hope to find true love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I think, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madison"]}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", ":", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Well, I think -- my second one which is, if I could give you five minutes back or just an hour, whatever it may be to relive the great moment of your life, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I would probably -- first, when I played Madison's (ph) (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Early '80s?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "It was two days before Band Aid, but I do it now so much better now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140210pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "I think -- did we do a press stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]